A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, Associates, Warren T. Lindquist papers FA102
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller papers, Associates, Warren T. Lindquist papers
1953-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David
Lindquist, Warren T.
FA102
34.22 Cubic Feet 82 letter-sized document boxes; 5 legal-sized document boxes; 1 flat box.
Custodial History
Records were originally accessioned by the Rockefeller family archive in 1970 and 1978. The collection was officially accessioned by Rockefeller Archive Center in 1990 as accession 1990:110.
Arrangement
Arranged in 2 series, by Accession.
Series 1: 1970 Accession. Series 2: 1978 Accession.
Scope and Contents Note
These records document Warren T. Lindquist's tenure as associate to David Rockefeller, from 1951 to 1977. He was particularly involved in Mr. Rockefeller's real estate investments and efforts to improve urban housing opportunities during the mid-twentieth century. Mr. Lindquist also served as Mr. Rockefeller's proxy with organizations focused on urban development in New York City and throughout the country, as reflected in the folders on the Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, the Embarcadero Center, Morningside Heights Inc., the Pacific Air Commerce Center, and Westbay Associates. Additionally, there are extensive files on Fazenda Bodoquena, a large cattle ranch in Brazil in which Mr. Rockefeller purchased an interest in 1962.
Biographical/Historical Note
Warren T. Lindquist joined David Rockefeller's staff in 1951 following several years as a direct investment analyst for the industrial development department of W. R. Grace and Company. Among his roles in Mr. Rockefeller's office, Mr. Lindquist served as vice president of the Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, vice president of Remedco of Morningside Heights Inc., and a partner in Westbay Associates during its development efforts in the San Francisco Bay Area.
Mr. Lindquist was born in 1919 and graduated from Lafayette College in 1940. He served in the U.S. Army from 1941 to 1945, reaching the rank of major. Immediately after WWII, he met David Rockefeller while they both were stationed in Paris. After resigning from Mr. Rockefeller's office in 1977, Mr. Lindquist served as Executive Director of the Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association and then as the first Assistant Secretary for Public and Indian Housing in the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Warren Lindquist died November 15, 2003.
- 1970 Accession, 1953-1975; 1
  - General Correspondence: A Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Clubs; invitations to speak; proposed projects.
  - General Correspondence: A Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ACTION-Urban America, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1962-1966 in GFT; WTL contribution as member; election of trustees; By-Laws as of April 28, 1967; urban design info; WTL serves as member of National Advisory Council; annual reports.
  - Africa: General and Programs, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Background information for a working file.
  - Africa: MIT Fellows, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Press releases; information re managing economic development; Fellows in Africa conference, August 5-20, 1961. WTL trip report re: real estate investment in Africa.
  - Africa: Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Fact sheets; WTL East Africa report; memos re tobacco and essential oils; information re International Finance Corp.
  - Africa: Ventures, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Africa Bank consultations; reports of meetings of Committee of Nine.
  - Alden, William, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Brochures.
  - Aldrich, Alexander (Sam), 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Invitation to DR to speak at Brooklyn Center, LIU, clipping.
  - General Correspondence: Ba-Bl, 1962-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Clippings; proposed projects.
  - Middle Atlantic Conference of Building Owners and Managers (BOMA), 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Brochures; registration list; bulletin of proceedings.
  - General Correspondence: Ca-Ce, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Proposed projects; invitations; contributions; press releases, pamphlets, clippings.
  - General Correspondence: Ch-Col, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Scope and Contents note
  - General Correspondence: Com-Cox, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence: Cr-Cu, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Urban affairs survey, grants, street academy, CMB testimony at hearings on Minority Business Interprise; art collection; CMB decides to go national; background information.
  - Chase Manhattan Bank: Clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Clippings
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    DR contributions; staff newsletters, minutes of meetings; luncheons.
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Letters to art galleries re: benefit gallery opening.
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council: World Trade Center, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Recommendations re proposed center; clippings and press releases; minutes of meetings; endorsements.
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Statements and position papers; press releases, minutes, calendars; dinners; DR contributions.
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Cities: Baltimore, Brooklyn, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Pamphlets; urban renewal and housing programs; civic center plans; educational institutions.
  - Cities: Chicago, Cleveland, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Cities: New York, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Information on city planning and construction, improvement plans; clippings, press releases, urban studies and reports; Downtown? Lower Manhattan Assoc.; transportation, tax studies; World Trade Center; Stock Exchange; Lindsay administration.
  - Cities: New York, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cities: New York, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Community Research and Development Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Brochures, financial statements.
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Meetings, brochures, 1969 annual report.
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Study Group, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    African Bloc Rivalries; discussion meeting reports.
  - Crocker Estate Company, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Information, clippings, list of officers.
  - General Correspondence: D Miscellaneous, 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Personal correspondence; proposed projects.
  - Dallas, Texas Corporation, 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Clippings; city plans for redevelopment; preliminary economic study.
  - Dominguez Estate Company, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Real estate development in Los Angeles; agreements.
  - Downtown Brooklyn Development Committee, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Inter-Institutional Cooperation in Brooklyn - action proposal; 1969 annual report.
  - General Correspondence: Ea-Ed, 1963-1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Proposed projects; clippings; Economic Opportunity Corp.; Edison Electric Institute-Area Development Committee.
  - General Correspondence: Eh-Ey, 1963-1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Proposed projects; clippings; Cleveland Development Foundation.
  - Economics; Equipment Leasing, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Clippings; economics reference file.
  - Execuplane, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Execuplane and proposals for new airport (STOL- Short Take-Off and Landing).
  - General Correspondence: F Miscellaneous, 1962-1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Requests for recommendations; suggested projects; information on business contacts.
  - Florida; Fuller and Company, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    No interest by DR in Florida real estate; decision not to invest in Fuller construction company.
  - General Correspondence: G Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Requests for recommendations; real estate proposals; information on business contacts.
  - General Correspondence: Ha-Hi, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Requests for recommendations; real estate and housing proposals; information on business contacts.
  - General Correspondence: Ho-Hu, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Hawaii, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    Decision not to invest in suggested Hawaiian real estate.
  - Housing and Development Administration, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    WTL served on Citizens Advisory Committee; minutes of meetings.
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    Architectural critic; her clippings.
  - General Correspondence: I Miscellaneous, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Industrial Communities, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    Proposal to encourage investment of private U.S. capital in commercial and industrial development of promising underdeveloped nations; information on Nigeria and other African nations; expansion of idea to U.S. and Latin America.
  - General Correspondence: J Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    Information on business contacts; requests for recommendations.
  - General Correspondence: K Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    Information on business contacts; requests for recommendations; real estate proposals.
  - General Correspondence: K Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 52a)
    Conditions Governing Access Note
    Restricted material
  - Kenya, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    Information on Kenya economy; Tancat Ltd. information 1960-1961.
  - General Correspondence: La, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - General Correspondence: Le-Lu, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - General Correspondence: Ma-Me, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - General Correspondence: Mi-Mu, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    Requests for recommendations; real estate proposals; information on business contacts; comments on problems of Pacific Air Center.
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    DR contribution toward purchase of Whitney Museum; possibility of using air rights over Museum for a commercial tower.
  - General Correspondence: N Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    Requests for recommendations; information on business contacts; real estate proposals.
  - New Orleans, 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    Descriptions of real estate project in New Orleans.
  - Nigeria: Crepe Rubber Plant Venture, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Proposed DR investment; no action.
  - Nigeria: Industrial Community Project, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    Plan for overall program of development.
  - Nigeria: Sawmill Venture, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    Proposed investment, no action.
  - Nigeria: Steel Mill Venture, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    Proposed investment; not done
  - Nigeria: Westinghouse, 1961; 1964 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    Possible investment; none made
  - Nigeria, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Nuclear Development Corporation, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    A personal investment by WTL; sold out in 1964.
  - General Correspondence: O Miscellaneous, 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    Real estate proposals; requests for recommendations; WTL friendship with L. O'Brien of ADT company.
  - Overseas, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    Reference material on overseas investments.
  - General Correspondence: Pa-Pi, 1962-1969 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - General Correspondence: Pl-Pu, 1962-1969 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    Scope and Contents notes
  - Philippines, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    Scope and Content Note
    Clippings; articles; DR interest in Philippines, American enterprise there, Laurel-Langley Agreement; Filipino politics.
  - Philippines, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Planning, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    Housing and Urban Development Act of 1965; "Cluster Developments", reports and clippings; "Land Economics.".
  - Public Relations; Pre-Fabs, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    HUD contest; public relations proposes opinion survey on "Rockefeller Image."
  - General Correspondence: Q Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    E. R. Quesada.
  - General Correspondence: Ra-Rh, 1962-1969 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    Proposed projects; clippings and articles.
  - General Correspondence: Ri-Ry, 1962-1969 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    Scope and Contents Note
  - Regional Plan Association, 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    Bulletins, press releases; proposed plans, conferences, invitations.
  - Regional Plan Association, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - General Correspondence: Sa-Sc, 1962-1970 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - General Correspondence: Se-Sh, 1962-1970 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    Proposed projects; personal correspondence.
  - General Correspondence: Si-So, 1962-1970 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - General Correspondence: St-Sw, 1962-1970 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    Scp[e and Contents Note
  - Sea Farm, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    "Under Sea Technology" and clipping.
  - Spencer, John, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Staff Meetings (Closed Folder), 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Staff Conference: Rockefeller Image, 1969 September (Box 13, Folder 89)
    "The Rockefeller Image: An Objective Appraisal"
  - General Correspondence: T Miscellaneous, 1963-1969 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Taxation; Tax Reform, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    Reference material on local and Federal taxes.
  - General Correspondence: U-V Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    Requests for recommendations; real estate proposals.
  - Uganda, 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Urban Renewal, 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    Printed material
  - Urban Renewal, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Urban Renewal and Housing, 1958; 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    Published reference materials on rehabilitation; NAR statement on urban housing.
  - General Correspondence: Wa-We, 1964-1969 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - General Correspondence: Wh-Wr, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Wall Street Foundation, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Westchester County Planning Board, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    WTL appointed member of the Board in January 1968; minutes of meetings; staff reports on zoning change appeals; brochures on county planning.
  - Westchester County Planning Board, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Westchester County Planning Board Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Westchester County Planning Board Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Westchester County Planning Board Publications, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Westchester County Planning Board Publications, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - General Correspondence: Y Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Box 16, Folder 106)
    Information on business contacts; requests for recommendations; investment proposals.
  - General Correspondence: Z Miscellaneous, 1959-1970 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - St. Bart's Property, 1958-1970 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    DR property in Virgin Islands; appraisals of property in 1966; sale of Gouveneur Property in 1969.
  - St. Bart's Property, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Embarcadero Center: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    Progress of building center in San Francisco.
  - Embarcadero Center: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Embarcadero Center: San Francisco Redevelopment Agency (SFRA), 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    Beginnings of Center, arrangements, progress.
  - Embarcadero Center: SFRA Good Faith Deposit, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    Attempt to replace cash deposit with letters of credit.
  - Embarcadero Center: Architect's Fees, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    DR and WR advance of 50 percent of fees due in 1969.
  - Embarcadero Center: Hotel Construction, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    Construction details
  - Embarcadero Center: Hotel Financing, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    Financing plans for hotel. Gironzentrale search for mortgage money.
  - Embarcadero Center: 230 Block Change Orders, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    Changes in construction specifications.
  - Embarcadero Center: 230 Block Documents, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    Copies of loan agreements with Metropolitan Life and Wells Fargo.
  - Embarcadero Center: 230 Block Draws from Construction Account, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    Withdrawals from loan account for construction.
  - Embarcadero Center: 230 Block Floor Plans (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Embarcadero Center: 230 Block Leasing Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    Rental of space in the building.
  - Embarcadero - Block 230 - Tax, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    1969 tax assessment
  - Embarcadero Center: Mortgage Loan Negotiations, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    Various proposals for raising $36 million dollars.
  - Embarcadero Center: Documents and Agreements, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    Joint venture agreement, purchase of land.
  - Embarcadero - Financial Statements, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    Auditors reports.
  - Embarcadero Center: Philanthropic Requests, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    Scattered appeals, no giving program established.
  - Embarcadero Center: Solicitation for Work and Interest in Participation, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    Job applicants; offers to supply services, equipment for construction.
  - Embarcadero Center: Solicitation for Work and Interest in Participation, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - Embarcadero Center: Topping Out Ceremony, 1970 February 4 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - Embarcadero Center: Brochures and Clippings, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymark Corporation: General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    The instrument through which DR and WR and also DR associates participate in Embarcadero project. Agreements on shares, payment of costs of project. Originally called Westbay, changed to Claymark. Personal information on WTL.
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymore Corporation: Directors Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    Incomplete set.
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymore Corporation: Stockholders Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    Copies of minutes.
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymore Corporation: Tax Returns, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    Copies of 1968 and 1969 returns.
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymore Corporation: In Lieu of Tax Payments, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    Payments to City of San Francisco.
  - Embarcadero Center: Claymore Corporation: Davis Street Station, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    Claymark helped subsidize subway station study.
  - National Housing Partnership: General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 137)
    Statement of goals and background material; proposal for National Consortium, Partnership agreement.
  - National Housing Partnership: General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - National Housing Partnership: Board of Directors, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 139)
    Draft of Prospectus, July 1969; report to the Board, January 21, 1970.
  - National Housing Partnership: Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 140)
    Clippings re: housing and OEO.
  - National Housing Partnership: Committee on Financing, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 141)
    Meetings; White House Statement September 9, 1968; proposals re financing, shares and partnership interest; joint meeting agenda.
  - National Housing Partnership: Committee on Staffing, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    Curricula vitae; appointment of committees.
  - National Housing Partnership: Meetings of Incorporators, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 143)
    Meetings, members, agenda, by-laws, articles of incorporation.
  - National Housing Partnership: Meetings of Incorporators, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - Urban America, Inc: "City" newsletter, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 145)
    Bi-monthly review.
  - Urban Coalition: General Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 147)
    Memos; background information; management and labor cooperation; reorganization of Urban Coalition; requests for funds; notices of meetings, invitations.
  - Urban Coalition: Assembling Housing Markets for New Building Systems, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 148)
    Discussions of housing problems; Savannah Plan. Separate: minutes of meetings of executive committee, task force on housing reconstruction and investment, steering committee.
  - Urban Coalition: Legislative Activity, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 149)
    Press releases; Housing and Urban Development Act of 1968; background material; summaries of pending legislation.
  - Urban Coalition: "Monthly Monitor", 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 150)
    Monthly collections of clippings and articles.
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: General Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 151)
    Drafts of memos, press releases, proposals of merger of Urban America and the Urban Coalition.
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Reference Material, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 152)
    Working papers, summaries and statements, related speeches. Housing Statistics Handbook of Mayor Lindsay, November 1967.
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Reference Material, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 153)
    Working papers, summaries and statements, related speeches.
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 154)
    Mortgage and labor problems, defense of construction unions
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Meeting Materials, 1968 June-July (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Meeting Materials, 1968 August-1968 September (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Meeting Materials, 1968 December (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Meeting Materials, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 158)
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Meeting Materials, 1970 January (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Subcommittee on Urban Housing Computer Models, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 160)
    Cost estimates of subsidized housing; UC-IBM housing cost study; background information, demonstration, reports, recommendations; UC position papers, addresses, clippings and press releases.
  - Urban Coalition: Task Force on Housing Reconstruction and Investment: Subcommittee on Urban Housing Computer Models, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 161)
  - Urban Coalition: Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 162)
    First annual report - 1968; consumer credit; report of health task force; program brochure.
  - Urban Coalition: Reports, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 163)
  - Urban Coalition Action Council: Statements and Newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 164)
    Pamphlet "Time to Wake Up"; statement to R.R. Ways and Means Committee; UCAC legislation bulletin.
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: John Fischer Material, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 165)
    Proposed budget, constitution; background for Westbay Community Assoc.; related articles.
  - Industrial Housing Systems: General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 166)
    Background information; working papers, clippings.
  - Industrial Housing Systems: MAPKA Progress Reports, 1964-1970 (Box 23, Folder 167)
    Reports; industrial agricultural community development for developing countries; CMB bulletins re: housing industry.
  - Urban Institute, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 168)
    Organized in Washington to study urban problems; WTL offered to help on informal basis.
  - Planning Commission and State Downtown Plans: Working File, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 169)
    State of New York's plans for Battery Park City for developing the lower end of Manhattan compared with plans for same area developed by NYC Planning Commission. 1967 agreement between State and City to work together.